<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="action_settings">action settings</string>
    <string name="app_name">Avatar Rules</string>

    <string-array name="genericRules">
        <item>No generic rule</item>
        <item>I haven\'t cleaned my room in a hundred years… not looking forward to that… for the rest of the game you must clear the empties (last one here)</item>
        <item>Genocide. That\'s rough shit, everyone drink out of respect for fallen. Except Zhao, that guy\'s a dick.</item>
        <item>Foam mouth guy, way too excited to be here, drink 2 to calm nerves</item>
        <item>"Letuce leaf?" Find something green and eat it like a crazy king.</item> <!-- Cabbage space -->
        <item>“I\'ll make sure Appa doesn\'t eat all of your hay” Regardless of who lands here Appa/Momo must drink 1</item>
        <item>No generic rule</item>
        <item>No generic rule</item>
        <item>Pick a card, if it is black, you find the waterbending scroll, drink a shot of shmirnoff ice. If the card is red, you find the bison whistle, drink a shot of champagne.</item> <!-- Cabbage space -->
        <item>Sokka\'s instincts are in charge on this space. Sokka rolls a die, drink that many.</item>
        <item>Just keep flyin\', jump over the great divide</item>
        <item>Same rules for everyone. Roll a die, 1–3 you remain in the Great Divide, 4–6 you have a chance to escape. Rules for rolled numbers follow:\n1-Your guide breaks his/her arm, pick someone, this person cannot use their arms as long as you are in the Great Divide, you must drink and roll from them.\n2-You are not allowed to bring food or drink into the canyon, finish your drink.\n3-The refugees are divided, you all want to get out! You are still stuck, but add 1 to your next roll. Drink 3 now.\4-You get 4 chances to bounce a ball into a cup. You must successfully bounce the ball into the cup twice in order to escape the Great divide. If you fail to make it twice you must drink 6.\n5-You get 5 chances to bounce a ball into a cup. You must successfully bounce the ball into the cup twice in order to escape the Great divide. If you fail to make it twice you must drink 8.\n6-You get 6 chances to bounce a ball into a cup. You must successfully bounce the ball into the cup twice in order to escape the Great divide. If you fail to make it twice you must drink 10.\nAfter you successfully escape the canyon roll once more to see how many spaces you move beyond (1=The Storm, 2=The Blue Spirit, etc…)</item>
        <item>Go to the Great Divide</item>
        <item>Go to the Great Divide</item>
        <item>Flashback episode! Tell a hilarious anecdote about someone playing about a time they got into trouble. Also, first person here receives Lightening Bending item.</item>
        <item>The Yu Yang archers are know for their accuracy, sink a ball in a cup from 10 feet, if you make it, give 5, if you miss, take 1</item>
        <item>Predict who will be the most drunk, make it so and give them a shot of vodka. (First person here only)</item>
        <item>Katara gets her necklace back, she can stop drinking 1 per turn now.</item>
        <item>No generic rule</item>
        <item>Special rule, look at other sheet and play game.</item>
        <item>No generic rule</item>
        <item>No generic rule</item>
        <item>No generic rule</item>
        <item>Draw 2 cards. Drink the 2 shots of the elements you draw mixed together.</item>
        <item>Where we haven\'t been, we\'ve heard about through story and song. Sing a song for the group. (Group\'s choice)</item>
        <item>Pentapox? I think I have heard of that. Tell 2 truths and a lie, people try to guess the lie. Take 2 drinks for every person who guesses correctly, give 2 for every incorrect guess.</item>
        <item>We are all connected. Everyone close their eyes. You must as a group count to 10, if 2 people speak at the same time, everyone drinks and you start over. You cannot speak if the person next to you just spoke.</item>
        <item>If you landed on foam mouth guy the first time, CHILL THE FUCK OUT. Finish your drink. If not, \'spin\' the wheel of punishment.</item>
        <item>THE BOULDER IS OVER HIS CONFLICTED FEELINGS… OF MAKING YOU DRINK. DRINK 2 SHOTS OF HARD CIDER</item>
        <item>Never give up without a fight… You find the knife, can now give 1 whenever you have to drink.</item>
        <item>No generic rule</item>
        <item>First to land here must be referred to as Foo Foo Cuddly Poops for the rest of the game</item>
        <item>Discover the date of the eclipse, drink the month number (September=9, May=5, etc.)</item>
        <item>Stuck in the desert. Every turn you attempt to get out.\nSpade: You make it out of the desert, drink the number on the card you drew / 2 rounded down shots of champagne.\nClubs: Attempt to bounce 2 balls into 2 cups simultaneously. You get X number of attempts, where X is value of card drawn / 2 rounded up. Failure is 2 shots of hard cider.\nDiamond: Stand 15 ft from someone, do not face them. Have them count to 3 and throw a ping pong ball in your direction, on 3 you must turn around and attempt to catch it in a cup. Success is an escape, failure drink 2 shots smirnoff.\nHeart: Correctly guess higher or lower for 3 more cards. Incorrect leads to a small pull of fireball.</item>
        <item>Stuck in the desert. Every turn you attempt to get out.\nSpade: You make it out of the desert, drink the number on the card you drew / 2 rounded down shots of champagne.\nClubs: Attempt to bounce 2 balls into 2 cups simultaneously. You get X number of attempts, where X is value of card drawn / 2 rounded up. Failure is 2 shots of hard cider.\nDiamond: Stand 15 ft from someone, do not face them. Have them count to 3 and throw a ping pong ball in your direction, on 3 you must turn around and attempt to catch it in a cup. Success is an escape, failure drink 2 shots smirnoff.\nHeart: Correctly guess higher or lower for 3 more cards. Incorrect leads to a small pull of fireball.</item>
        <item>Stuck in the desert. Every turn you attempt to get out.\nSpade: You make it out of the desert, drink the number on the card you drew / 2 rounded down shots of champagne.\nClubs: Attempt to bounce 2 balls into 2 cups simultaneously. You get X number of attempts, where X is value of card drawn / 2 rounded up. Failure is 2 shots of hard cider.\nDiamond: Stand 15 ft from someone, do not face them. Have them count to 3 and throw a ping pong ball in your direction, on 3 you must turn around and attempt to catch it in a cup. Success is an escape, failure drink 2 shots smirnoff.\nHeart: Correctly guess higher or lower for 3 more cards. Incorrect leads to a small pull of fireball.</item>
        <item>Cabbage Space</item> <!-- Cabbage Space -->
        <item>No generic rule</item>
        <item>In Ba Sing Se-You cannot ask questions\nJust a bear… This place is weird. Go around in a circle naming any hybrid animal named in the show. If you can\'t think of one, you are out. First out drinks 5, second drinks 4, etc.</item>
        <item>In Ba Sing Se-You cannot ask questions\nCabbage Space</item>
        <item>In Ba Sing Se-You cannot ask questions\nEscape from the circus, battle a boar-q-pine, and have a run-in with Azula. Flip a cup, bounce a ball into a cup, and attempt to draw a red card. For each failure drink half the value of the card you drew.</item>
        <item>In Ba Sing Se-You cannot ask questions</item>
        <item>In Ba Sing Se-You cannot ask questions</item>
        <item>In Ba Sing Se-You cannot ask questions</item>
        <item>MANDATORY STOP\nIn Ba Sing Se-You cannot ask questions\nOnce Aang reaches this space, start the song Thunderstruck. One person starts drinking, when the song says "thunder" or "thunderstruck", you stop and the next person starts, keep going until song is over.</item>
        <item>No generic rule</item>
        <item>Culture Clash! Draw 2 cards. Drink the 2 shots of the elements you draw mixed together.</item>
        <item>Assuming that fits into Sokka\'s master schedule… Anyone on this space must ask Sokka for permission to do things. (Go to the bathroom, drink, etc.)</item>
        <item>It\'s SO hot… How hot is it? I don\'t know, real hot? Tell a bad joke and everyone drink one.</item>
        <item>The person who hasn\'t been to the beach in the longest amount of time finishes their drink. (Only one time per game)</item>
        <item>Battling the elements was hard enough, but I had to do it while I could barely breathe. Smoke something. Or drink 6</item>
        <item>First person here is called Sparky Sparky Boom Man for the rest of the game, and can assign 1 shot of fireball now.</item>
        <item>Tell a scary story, if it sucks or you can\'t think of one, drink 4. Also, first person here unlocks Bloodbending! You can now make people drink 1 per turn.</item>
        <item>"What was your dream about?" Living underwater… Sounds Neat! Start a waterfall.</item>
        <item>You get Aang\'s new glider (view Aang\'s New Glider in skills and objects descriptions)</item>
        <item>No generic rule</item>
        <item>If you are Sparky Sparky Boom Man, Sokka hits you square in the head with a boomerang, and you blow up. Finish your drink.</item>
        <item>No generic rule</item>
        <item>No generic rule</item>
        <item>"Hey, RIOT!"</item>
        <item>No generic rule</item>
        <item>Cabbage Space\nWhile on this space, you must overdramatize everything you do. Penalty of one drink.</item>
        <item>First person here triggers 20 cups of 4 beers round of Rage Cage</item>
        <item>No generic rule</item>
        <item>No generic rule</item>
        <item>No generic rule</item>
        <item>Everyone finish their individual drinks. Mix the remaining champagne, cider and Shmirnoff; pass mixture around table until gone.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="aangRules">
        <item>Will you go penguin sledding with me? Pick one person to drink with you (one each)</item>
        <item>Avatar State - Take a drink of the Avatar State\n"I bet you\'ve never fought an airbender before… I bet I could take you both with my hands behind my back" Get on your knees and roll to see who feeds you a shot of champagne.</item>
        <item>Avatar State - Take a drink of the Avatar State\n"The Avatar has returned", everyone drink 1</item>
        <item>Don\'t ride the unagi, not fun… You almost drown, drink 1 shot of smirnoff</item>
        <item>Need to pass three deadly challenges, pick three people to drink. And complement someones outfit.</item>
        <item>Fire coal through an air funnel. Drink a shot of champagne mixed with a shot of hard cider.</item>
        <item>In Spirit World-You can neither show emotion nor use the bathroom.\nGet backhanded into tomorrow by Hei Bai, let the person to your left smack you in the face, then you both drink 1</item>
        <item>Avatar State - Take a drink of the Avatar State\nMeet with your past life, Avatar Roku. Drink 3 with anyone who has played this game as Aang before. If no one has, everyone finishes their drinks because fuck you.</item>
        <item>You spend 1 of your 3 copper pieces on a bison whistle, which saves your ass on multiple occasions. Drink 1 now, immune to next time someone makes you drink.</item>
        <item>Sokka\'s just jealous because he doesn\'t have an arrow. Draw an arrow on your forehead and drink 1.</item>
        <item>No specific rule</item>
        <item>No specific rule</item>
        <item>No specific rule</item>
        <item>No specific rule</item>
        <item>We need you, Aang… To get drunk. Drink 3 from Avatar State</item>
        <item>Duel Zhao with Zuko as your ally. Mini game of flip cup, Zhao has to do 6 cups, Aang and Zuko have to do 3 each. Loser(s) moves back 3 spaces.</item>
        <item>"Sometimes I forget what a powerful bender that kid is." Do some push-ups</item>
        <item>Sit away from the table until your next turn, you cannot be trusted. Also, drink 2, dick</item>
        <item>Concentrate on you leaf, light a candle and walk around the room until your next turn.</item>
        <item>I laugh at gravity all the time, haha, gravity. See generic</item>
        <item>Why are you wearing that at the north pole? Take a small pull of fireball to warm up.</item>
        <item>In Spirit World-You can neither show emotion nor use the bathroom.\nI figure since you\'ve found time to play with house pets, you must have already mastered waterbending? Draw a card, if it is a diamond, move ahead 1 space. If it isn\'t, drink 2 and lose a turn.</item>
        <item>Avatar State – Take a drink of the Avatar State\nYou go full avatar state. Have everyone roll a die, 1–3 they bow down, 4–6 they don\'t, and drink 3. You drink 2 for each person who bowed.</item>
        <item>Avatar State - Take a drink of the Avatar State\nThis rare chi-enhancing tea is a natural stimulant. In an ordinary warrior, it improves strength and energy ten-fold. In you, it may induce the Avatar State. Drink an energy drink or 5 hr energy.</item>
        <item>You make one fine octopus, drink without your thumbs for the next 2 turns, drink 2 now.</item>
        <item>No specific rule</item>
        <item>No specific rule</item>
        <item>No specific rule</item>
        <item>"Don\'t answer to Twinkle Toes, it\'s not manly!" You have to tip-toe wherever you go for the rest of the game. Also drink a shot of hard cider.</item>
        <item>Lose a turn</item>
        <item>Im not running. Both you and Azula draw two cards, highest sum wins, if you win, Azula drinks 2 shots chapagne. If she wins, you take a half shot of fireball.</item>
        <item>MANDATORY STOP\nYou must overcome your earthbending block, successfully flip 3 cups in a row, drink a shot of cider for every failed attempt. (8 max)</item>
        <item>In a past life you were left-handed, for the rest of the game drink with you off hand. Practice now and drink 3.</item>
        <item>No specific rule</item>
        <item>No specific rule</item>
        <item>No specific rule</item>
        <item>Abandon hope… of getting out of this game sober, drink 5.</item>
        <item>Both you and Azula cut the deck of cards, highest card wins (aces high). Loser drinks a mixture of one shot of hard cider and one shot of shmirnoff.</item>
        <item>Avatar Aang! How you do go on. You must act classy, drink with your pinky up the rest of the game.</item>
        <item>Tape a stuffed animal to your head (If sokka is already wearing it just drink 2)</item>
        <item>No specific rule</item>
        <item>Reunited with Appa! "I missed you, buddy" Take a drink with the person who was Appa and hug it out.</item>
        <item>Take out a whole earth kingdom army, give out one drink per player in the game.</item>
        <item>You must unlock your chakras. Attempt to bounce a ball into a cup 7 times, adding 2 cups to the stack each time, drink 2 for each failed attempt.</item>
        <item>Everyone must stop on this space. The challenge between the 4 players must only be completed once. Challenge: 6 cup game of flip cup, 1 beer per side.</item>
        <item>"I have hair?!" the person with the longest hair drinks 2</item>
        <item>Tada! Normal kid. Act like a sober version of yourself. If you aren\'t drunk enough, drink 5.</item>
        <item>Destroy a fire nation factory, every firebender drinks 2.</item>
        <item>"I think I\'m a little old to be fighting the Avatar." Duel the oldest person, best 5 card poker hand. Loser drinks 4.</item>
        <item>Attacked by Sparky Sparky Boom Man! Roll a die, if 1–4, he catches you, drink 3. Otherwise give 1.</item>
        <item>In Spirit World-You can neither show emotion nor use the bathroom.\nAir surfing! I can\'t believe I never thought of that! Drink 2 shots champagne.</item>
        <item>"I got to say, Sokka, you continue to impress me with your ideas." Have Sokka roll a die, you drink that many</item>
        <item>Helping people, that\'s what I do. Until your next turn, you split the drinking punishments of the other players. (If they have to drink 4, you both drink 2)</item>
        <item>Roll a die to decide who you challenge to best 2 out of 3 in blackjack. If you win, Firelord Ozai forgot his pants, if you lose, you do. (Loser takes off pants for two turns)</item>
        <item>You sleep like a baby moose-lion. Make sure that happens tonight, and drink 4. </item>
        <item>MANDATORY STOP\nThree way race between Aang, Toph and Azula, split a hard cider into 3 cups. You must drink, bounce a ball in the cup, and flip it. Losers lose a turn.</item>
        <item>Can you trust Zuko? If he sided with you in Crossroads of Destiny, give 3. If you lost or didn\'t dual, take 3.</item>
        <item>Play Ring of fire. Drink and pass the fireball everytime Ring of Fire is said. (Play song)</item>
        <item>Aang does 10 hot squats every time someone lands here… nobody else got homework…</item>
        <item>"Sounds like a crazy fishing trip" your only line in the episode. Everyone who has caught a fish drinks.</item>
        <item>Try to teach Katara about forgiveness, forgive someone in the room for a minor slight. And drink, because this is a drinking game.</item>
        <item>Did I mention that I\'m an incurable prankster? Switch two people\'s drinks.</item>
        <item>MANDATORY STOP\nAvatar State, Yip Yip! Have Toph pick you up and drink a shot of avatar state.</item>
        <item>MANDATORY STOP\nGain wisdom from the past avatars. Roll a die, if it is an even, move on, if it is an odd, draw a card and take a shot of whatever element you drew.</item>
        <item>MANDATORY STOP\nIt is time for you to face the fire lord. Flip 2 coins. If they are both heads, move forward. Otherwise drink 2, and 2 additional for every turn you have been stuck here.</item>
        <item>MANDATORY STOP\nUnblock your final chakra and enter avatar state. Set up 3 cups beer pong style. You get 2 shots per turn, when you get all 3 cups, the game is over. Drink a drink of avatar state every turn.</item>
        <item>No specific rule</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="kataraRules">
        <item>Crack open an iceberg in anger, splash the person to the left of you in the face with a cup of ice water. You both drink one</item>
        <item>"Aang has brought us something we haven\'t had in a long time… Fun." Sing the FUN song from Spongebob, every person who doesn\'t know the words drinks 2.</item>
        <item>(To Aang) "Sokka and I, we\'re your family now." the 3 of you drink 2 a piece.</item>
        <item>Save Aang from drowning, you and him draw a card, low card drinks 2.</item>
        <item>Encased in rock candy, lose a turn</item>
        <item>Give an inspirational speech, group drink out of respect. Lose your necklace, drink 1 extra per turn until you get it back. (once you pass Bato of the Water Tribe you can stop) drinking 1 extra)</item>
        <item>Give Aang hope… of leaving this game sober, drink half of his assigned drinks until end of book 1.</item>
        <item>You might as well face it, laddy, we\'re going with you. Do your Gimli impression and drink 3.</item>
        <item>Captured by pirates. Actually, it kind of is all your fault, drink 2.</item>
        <item>“I’ve never bent water I couldn’t see before.” Blindly take one of three shots (Vodka, Shmirnoff Ice, and Water) On top of that, you are a liar because you cleared Aangs lungs of water in Warriors of Kyoshi so take an extra drink</item>
        <item>No specific rule</item>
        <item>No specific rule</item>
        <item>No specific rule</item>
        <item>No specific rule</item>
        <item>Hot cinders! Take a small pull of fireball.</item>
        <item>You sent Momo to get water but he keeps bringing back random shit, drink a little of Appa/Momo\'s drink.</item>
        <item>Eat some papaya (or whatever fruit you can find). If no fruit around, drink 2.</item>
        <item>Get hit with Nyla\'s paralysing tongue, drink 2</item>
        <item>Bitch you got burned, take a small pull of fireball, then cool it off with some soothing Shmirnoff ice because you discovered your healing.</item>
        <item>You are flying!! Drink 1 shot of champagne, and feel that airbending.</item>
        <item>Duel with Master Pakku. You lose, take 2 shots of Smirnoff Ice. Give 1 though, because you did pretty good.</item>
        <item>"Katara, you\'ve advanced more quickly than any student I\'ve ever trained." Move ahead 1 space and take 2 shots of smirnoff.</item>
        <item>Five card draw (poker) against Zuko. If you win Zuko drinks a Smirnoff. If you lose, you drink some fireball (1 shot) </item>
        <item>Drug underground by an earth bender. Beer bong a hard cider. Cause for real, you rolled a one…</item>
        <item>Is this real? Or a legend? Oh, it\'s a real legend. Become a legend and finish your drink.</item>
        <item>No specific rule</item>
        <item>No specific rule</item>
        <item>No specific rule</item>
        <item>"This is just going to be a bunch of guys chucking rocks at each other, isn\'t it?" Drink a shot of hard cider</item>
        <item>Lose a turn</item>
        <item>We could have gotten some sleep earlier if toph didnt have such issues. Drink a shot of cider</item>
        <item>"You never call me Sifu Katara…" Aang has to call you Sifu for the rest of the game. (In addition to your name)</item>
        <item>You think you were the first people to think their war was justified? Finsih your drink and think about that shit.</item>
        <item>No specific rule</item>
        <item>No specific rule</item>
        <item>No specific rule</item>
        <item>Finish your drink to steady your hands. You help deliver a child… Whose name is hope. There is so much fuckin hope going around! Everyone cheers together… To hope! </item>
        <item>Just bend the slurry woman! Drink a mix of a shot of Smirnoff Ice mixed mixed with a shot of hard cider</item>
        <item>"I\'m Kwa Mai, and this is… Dum" Smooth move on the aliases, whenever someone talks to Toph, they have to call her dumb, otherwise penalty of a drink.</item>
        <item>Bonding time with Toph, you are now mated for the rest of the game. (Only on normal drinks, no elemental or finish drinks)</item>
        <item>No specific rule</item>
        <item>Jet\'s back. Roll a die, 1 or 2 you trust him, give 3. 3–6 you don\'t trust him, take 2.</item>
        <item>Sorry! We\'re actually on your side! Make someone drink 3, but feel really bad about it, so drink 3 as well.</item>
        <item>Ty lee chi-blocks you! Roll a die, on a 1, you defend yourself, gain a turn. Otherwise, drink 3 and lose a turn.</item>
        <item>Challenge with Aang, Zuko, and Azula. See Special Rules (to the right)</item>
        <item>You need a healing session. give aang a back massage and drink 5.</item>
        <item>Sapphire Fire, nice to meet you. Take a pull of fireball, Sapphire Fire.</item>
        <item>You are the Painted Lady! Drink 4 now and help out the other players for the rest of the game. (Refilling drinks, etc.)</item>
        <item>"I-It\'s so hot, it\'s so hot… Momo is shedding like Appa." I guess jokes don\'t run in the family… Drink 2 for every sibling or pet you have.</item>
        <item>Attacked by Sparky Sparky Boom Man! Roll a die, if 1–4, he catches you, drink 3. Otherwise give 1.</item>
        <item>Oh Sokka, just hold hands. Aang, Katara, Sokka, and Toph all drink together until your next turn.</item>
        <item>Locked up in a wooden prison, using your own sweat as bending water. Start sweating, and take a shot of vodka.</item>
        <item>Drink 4. Also, until your next turn, you must feed everyone their drinks.</item>
        <item>These yoga poses work wonders in extreme heat… Nice. Take a swig of fireball and do the downward dog yoga pose, get that ass up, girl. (Google it if you don\'t know)</item>
        <item>The Katara-Appa combo is dangerous, you save everyone\'s ass. Drink for everyone until your next turn, except Azula and Zuko because they suck.</item>
        <item>MANDATORY STOP\nThe rest of the gang is fighting Azula, you are stuck tending to your father.Until the finale, you have to take care of everyone in the gang. Get them drinks/food and stuff (Not Azula). Also, drink 5 so you are not left out.</item>
        <item>Everyone go around in a circle pointing out a flaw in Zuko. Group drink.</item>
        <item>You know, how it would\'ve been nice for us if you lost your firebending a long time ago. You are immune to fireball the rest of the game. Take a shot of it now for old times though.</item>
        <item>You didn\'t get any homework, But drink 5 anyway.</item>
        <item>Reunited with your father. Drink 1 for every letter in your dad\'s name.</item>
        <item>MANDATORY STOP\nTake revenge on someone who has wronged you. Whoever has made you drink the most over the course of the game has to finish their drink. But finish yours too, because fuck it.</item>
        <item>My heart is so full of hope, that it\'s making me tearbend! Tell a sad story to the group.</item>
        <item>MANDATORY STOP\nThen, Katara and Zuko charge in with some liquidy hot offense. Draw a card, if it is black, drink a shot of smirnoff and move forward. If it is red, take a drink of fireball and stay put.</item>
        <item>MANDATORY STOP\nMeet with the members of the White Lotus, take a drink of every element and move forward.</item>
        <item>MANDATORY STOP\nYou go to help Zuko fight Azula, then you get benched. Draw a card, if it is a face card, move forward. Otherwise drink half the value of the card.</item>
        <item>MANDATORY STOP\nYou must defeat Azula by chaining her up. Put some smirnoff in 3 cups of yours, and she gets 3 empty cups. You must beat her in flip cup. If you win, the game is over, if you lose, stay put and try again next turn. For every 2 fails, she has to flip another cup.</item>
        <item>No specific rule</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="sokkaRules">
        <item>Why is it every time you play with water i get wet?! Drink a shot of smirnoff ice</item>
        <item>I\'m just a guy with a boomerang... I didn\'t ask for all this flying and magic! If you have ever thrown a boomerang, give 3, if you haven\'t, take 3.</item>
        <item>Learn how to play air ball the hard way. Drink a shot of champagne.</item>
        <item>Meet Suki and act like a jerk. Share an anecdote about someone you wronged in the past, everyone drinks in apology.</item>
        <item>Encased in rock candy, lose a turn</item>
        <item>You large eared cretin! Whoever has the biggest ears must drink 2.</item>
        <item>In Spirit World-You can neither show emotion nor use the bathroom.\nYou really have to go to the bathroom, don\'t you? Too bad, fill up your bladder, drink 3.</item>
        <item>You might as well face it, laddy, we\'re going with you. Do your Gimli impression and drink 3.</item>
        <item>"While you guys are playing in the water, I\'m supposed to be cleaning the mud out of a giant bison\'s feet? Mud and bugs. Ok." Flip a coin, heads you rub appa\'s feet, tails he rubs yours.</item>
        <item>You know who could take that drink for you? Sokka’s instincts. While on this square, you drink for everyone.</item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
        <item>"This was in my dream. We shouldn\'t go to the market. Food eats people! Also Momo could talk, you said some very unkind things." No eating until Book 2, and make Momo drink 3.</item>
        <item>Sokka thinks he is an earthbender, "take that you rock." Drink 1 shot of hard cider.</item>
        <item>Can your science explain how it rains? Yes! Yes it can! Make it rain, start a waterfall.</item>
        <item>Get hit with Nyla\'s paralysing tongue, drink 2</item>
        <item>Katara gives you the mopey mask, pout until your next turn. Drink 3 in sadness.</item>
        <item>See Generic.</item>
        <item>Perhaps we can do an activity together? Choose someone to drink 2 with you.</item>
        <item>"Appa and I go way back, don\'t we buddy?" Drink 2 with Appa.</item>
        <item>My girl friend turned into the moon. shotgun a beer outside by yourself, cry a little and think about your life. If you can see the moon everyone else shotgun a beer afterward.</item>
        <item>Katara gets magic spirit water, Aang gets waterbending scrolls, and you get a pat on the back. Take care, son. Have everyone say something they are proud of you for, drink after each one.</item>
        <item>Don\'t let the cave-in get you down, Sokkaaa. You just need a clown! Take a shot of cider to stay strong.</item>
        <item>See generic</item>
        <item>See generic</item>
        <item>See generic</item>
        <item>Two words: ~Water Tribe~ Everyone but you and Katara drink 3</item>
        <item>Lose a turn</item>
        <item>I\'ve never not slept before... what if i fall asleep now and something happens... and something always happens! drink 2 and chill the fuck out.</item>
        <item>Fuck up while hunting Foo Foo Cuddly Poops. Tape a stuffed animal to your head.</item>
        <item>Its called Sokka style, learn it. For the rest of the game, any time anyone says the word "who" you must strike them in the head with a book.</item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
        <item>Roll up your sleeves for the rest of the game... Sleeveless guy.</item>
        <item>Together, we\'re Team Avatar! Everyone drinks.</item>
        <item>Avatar Aang! How you do go on. You must act classy, drink with your pinky up the rest of the game.</item>
        <item>Recite a Haiku. If not 5 7 5 drink 5. If is, give 5.</item>
        <item></item>
        <item>Did Jet... Die? You know, it was really unclear. Roll a die, drink that many.</item>
        <item>I don\'t like the new positive Sokka... Long Feng brainwashed you! Didn\'t he? Give someone a compliment and drink together.</item>
        <item>Reunite with your father. Tell a story about your dad, and everyone drinks in honor, accept Katara because that bitch has daddy issues.</item>
        <item>"Just take the bear" See Special Rules (to the right)</item>
        <item>It\'s Sokka\'s plan... To get wasted. Drink 4.</item>
        <item>Names Fire... Wang Fire. Take a pull of fireball, Wang Fire.</item>
        <item>Do you want the one headed fish? Or the 2 headed? Roll a die, 1-3 drink 4, 4-6 drink 2 give 2.</item>
        <item>MANDATORY STOP\nBuild a sword out of a meteor, paint a picture, and get in a sword fight. Pretty busy day. 3 attempts to bounce a ball in a cup, sink a ball from across the table into a 6 cup triangle, and challenge someone to 3 cup flip cup. Drink 2 for each failure, and loser loses turn.</item>
        <item>Attacked by Sparky Sparky Boom Man! Roll a die, if 1-4, he catches you, drink 3. Otherwise give 1.</item>
        <item>Are there any bathrooms in the spirit world? As a matter of fact, there are not. For the rest of the game, if you need to go to the bathroom, finish your drink first.</item>
        <item>Get a pet hawk. Choose one person to call Hawky, make them get you things for the rest of the game.</item>
        <item>Your arm has a mind of its own! You have been bloodbent, you can\'t use your arms untill next turn... And drink 2. (find a way)</item>
        <item>Perhaps you would like to scream into this pillow? Give Aang a pillow, have him scream in it, then both drink 2.</item>
        <item>You suck at public speaking. Loosen up! Drink 3 for courage.</item>
        <item>MANDATORY STOP\nWe need to be fast, careful, and lucky. Set up 3 cups, 2 with water 1 with fireball. You must blindly drink 2.</item>
        <item>Yeah! Boomerang! If a player has been declared Sparky Sparky Boom Man, you kill them, make them finish their drink.</item>
        <item>All we need to do is make Zuko angry! Easy enough. Make Zuko drink 2.</item>
        <item>My last girlfriend turned into the moon. Split a beer with Zuko and hug it out. (Preferably blue moon)</item>
        <item>"Sokka, there\'s no prison in the world that can hold two Water Tribe geniuses." Then you better find two... Drink 2 shots smirnoff</item>
        <item>Hold a flower in your mouth until your next turn</item>
        <item>Flying Kick-a-pow, drink 5</item>
        <item>Team Avatar! Air! Water! Earth! Fire! Heart? Draw a card, if it is a heart, move forward. If it isn\'t, take a drink of avatar state.</item>
        <item>Whats our destiny today? Find out. Draw a card, if it is black, move forward, if it is red, roll a die and drink that many.</item>
        <item>"Attention, crew, this is your captain speaking. Everyone please report to the bomb bay immediately for hot cakes and sweet cream. We have a very special birthday to celebrate." Roll a die, draw a card, drink the difference, move forward.</item>
        <item>"I don\'t think boomerang is coming back." Make a trick ping pong ball shot, and choose someone to try to make it. If they do, roll a die and drink that many. If they don\'t they can choose either themselves or you to "prove it". If you win the proving, you win the game.</item>
        <item>"I\'m trying to capture the moment!" Take a picture of the gaang and all of their drunken glory.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="zukoRules">
        <item>You want to learn advanced firebending already? You asked for it, take a shot of fireball.</item>
        <item>Aang flips you with airbending up against the wall... Ouch, drink a shot of champagne.</item>
        <item>Agni Kai against Zhao, take turns drawing random cards, first to 5 reds wins, drink for every black you pull. Loser drinks 1 and loses a turn.</item>
        <item>Attempt to burn down Kyoshi Island roll a die, 1-3 you burn it down, drink a shot of fireball. 4-6 Aang puts it out, take a shot of Smirnoff Ice.</item>
        <item>The fire nation has yet to reach Omashu, drink 1 for each person ahead of you.</item>
        <item>You are close on the trail of the Avatar, add one to your next roll</item>
        <item>You are clearly outnumbered, you are clearly outmatched. zuko and iroh against aang katara soka and appa/momo. 4 cup flip cup, one beer each side. Losers lose a turn (only do once)</item>
        <item>You trick Zhao with your smokescreen. Make him drink 1</item>
        <item>Uncle wastes your time looking for his lotus tile... You lose a turn, but you find a lotus tile.</item>
        <item>Does the Fire Nation let people go? Does the Fire Nation have mercy? Drink 2</item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
        <item>You will learn respect, and suffering will be your teacher. Fireball to the face (take a small pull). Draw the scar on your face, the mark of the banished prince.</item>
        <item>Duel Zhao with Aang as you ally. Mini game of flip cup, Zhao has to do 6 cups, Aang and Zuko have to do 3 each.</item>
        <item>That volcano erupted even hotter than your temper. Drink 2 to give props.</item>
        <item>Enlist Junes help in finding the avatar, pick someone to drink 2 with you.</item>
        <item>This is the only episode you are not in, but Zhao is. Make that guy drink 3.</item>
        <item>See generic</item>
        <item>Pirates come after you and you fake your death. Drink 2 and lay on the ground.</item>
        <item>Remember your breath of fire, it could save your life out there... Drink a small pull of fireball.</item>
        <item>Five card draw (poker) against Katara. If you win Katara drinks some fireball (1 shot). If she wins, you drink a Smirnoff.</item>
        <item>You lied to me! Duel Azula. Split a beer, chugging contest. Loser misses their next turn.</item>
        <item>If the Earth Kingdom discovers us, they\'ll have us killed... But if the Fire Nation discovers us, we\'ll be turned over to Azula... Earth Kingdom it is! Take a shot of hard cider.</item>
        <item>See generic</item>
        <item>See generic</item>
        <item>See generic</item>
        <item>Fire Nation Man! "Fire Lord, my flame burns for thee!" Go back to the Fire Nation! Take a shot of hard cider.</item>
        <item>MANDATORY STOP\nThis is your episode and it is pretty badass. Bounce a ball and try to knock it into a cup with a butter knife. 5 attempts, drink a shot of fireball for every miss.</item>
        <item>Hes just an angry freak with a pony tail. Drink one per player who has a pony tail.</item>
        <item>You learn about the 4 elements, and how to redirect lightning. Take a half shot of each element, you may now assign 1 drink per turn.</item>
        <item>Move forward into the desert</item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
        <item>"I\'m tired of living like this." Steal from the rich and give to the poor. Make the least drunk person finish someone elses drink.</item>
        <item>"What are you doing firebending your tea? For a wise, old man, that was a pretty stupid move!" Finally, you can give Iroh shit. Iroh drinks 5. If no Iroh, everyone drinks.</item>
        <item>You want a show? I\'ll give you a show. Duel Jet, flip a coin. If you win, drink 4, if you lose, give 4.</item>
        <item>Go on a "date" with someone. Split a drink of your choice and sit away from the group for a turn.</item>
        <item></item>
        <item>It is time for you to look inward, and start asking the big questions: Who are you? And what do you want? Choose someone to trade drinks with. Try them out, 1 drink a piece.</item>
        <item>"What you did beneath that lake. It was in such conflict with your image of yourself that you are now at war within your own mind and body." Draw a card, drink a shot of the element.</item>
        <item>You are in an unusually good mood, pick someone to drink 2 with you.</item>
        <item>It is time for you to choose your destiny. Roll a die, on 1-3, ally with Katara, on 4-6 you ally with Azula. See Special Rules (to the right)</item>
        <item>Take the credit for killing Aang, take a shot of Avatar state.</item>
        <item>You are so beautiful when you hate the world. Say something that you hate, give someone a compliment, and drink 2.</item>
        <item>The fire nation is polluting the crap out of that river, take a drink of something you don\'t want to take a drink of.</item>
        <item>Some episodes take place in the fire nation but don\'t feature firebenders... Drink 2 I guess.</item>
        <item>Tell a revealing story about your past - everyone drink one in recognition.</item>
        <item>"The Fire Sages keep the secret history in the Dragonbone Catacombs." Go on a spiritual quest, draw a card, if red, give that many, if black, drink that many.</item>
        <item>Not in this episode :( drink 2.</item>
        <item>Not in this episode either! Drink 2, or finish your drink if you landed on The Runaway.</item>
        <item>It\'s not a prince\'s place to walk anywhere... Pick 2 people to carry you somewhere of your choosing.</item>
        <item>"Perhaps I\'ve made some bad choices, but today I\'m going to set it right." Lay out 5 cards face down, play higher/lower and drink 2 for each one you get wrong.</item>
        <item>MANDATORY STOP\nAttempt to redirect lightning. Using your off hand, bounce a ping pong ball into a cup. 10 attempts to make 5, if successful give a shot of fireball, if not, take one.</item>
        <item>Do your best impression of the person playing as Azula and Iroh. Everyone drinks.</item>
        <item>Play Ring of Fire. Drink and pass the fireball evertime Ring of Fire is said (Play song)</item>
        <item>That\'s rough, buddy. Split a beer with Sokka and hug it out. (Preferably blue moon)</item>
        <item>Small skirmish with your evil sister, play rock, paper, scissors. Loser drinks 2</item>
        <item>You look like a ninja this episode. Anyone wearing black drinks 2. If no one is, you drink 4</item>
        <item>Pretty good Zuko costume... But your scar is on the wrong side... Drink with your non-dominant hand from now on. If someone catches you, finish the drink.</item>
        <item>Then, Katara and Zuko charge in with some liquidy hot offense. Draw a card, if it is red, take a drink of fireball and move forward. If it is black, take a shot of smirnoff and stay put.</item>
        <item>Reuinite with Iroh after betraying him. He tells you that you must become fire lord today. Draw a card, if it is a face card or an ace, move forward. If not, roll a die and drink that many.</item>
        <item>The showdown that was always meant to be. Agni Kai! Face off against Azula one last time. Take turns bouncing a ball into a cup. Every time you make it, add another cup to the stack. If you miss twice in a row, you are out. If you win, move forward, if you lose, drink 1 for every cup in the stack.</item>
        <item>You become the new Fire Lord, congrats! Draw a card, if it is royalty, drink a shot of fireball. If it isn\'t, finish your drink. You win the game.</item>
        <item></item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="tophRules">
        <item>Appa is a bit too tired to fly, lose a turn</item>
        <item>Yip yip motherfucker. Add 2 to your next roll, take a drink, and hold on tight.</item>
        <item>Lemur! Momo was added to the party. Pick a companion to drink 2 with you.</item>
        <item>"I promised the girls I would give them a ride on Appa!" All the ladies in the room drink 2, if there are none, all you men drink 4.</item>
        <item>Ate too many apples at feast, too fat to fit through the ventilation pipe, drink 2</item>
        <item>“That lemur… its earthbending…” drink 2 shots of hard cider</item>
        <item>Appa can\'t see Aang when he\'s in the spirit world. Drink 1 per turn until Aangs turn</item>
        <item>You catch a fish! Drink 2 give 1</item>
        <item>"Don\'t get too happy, you gotta do me next" Flip a coin, heads Sokka rubs your feet, tails he rubs yours.</item>
        <item>"Thanks Momo, I owe you a bushel of apples." Hold her to that! Drink 2 with Katara.</item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
        <item>You get frozen for 100 years. Drink 1 shot of smirnoff mixed with 1 shot of champagne.</item>
        <item>"You know what I like most about Appa? His sense of humor. Tell a good joke. Everyone drinks if it is good, bad jokes will be punished by 5 drinks.</item>
        <item>The voice of Toph makes an appearance as Meng, stalk Aang, drink whatever he drinks for the next two turns on top of what you have to drink.</item>
        <item>Get hit 4 times with Nyla\'s tongue, take 4 x 2 drinks</item>
        <item>Hide behind something until your next turn. Give 3 drinks.</item>
        <item>See generic</item>
        <item>Your foot gets frozen, take a shot of Smirnoff.</item>
        <item>Help Aang take out fire navy ships, make Zuko, Zhao, and Iroh drink a shot of champagne.</item>
        <item>Zhao, the invincible. Jump on his head and ruin that bastards day. Pick a card and both of you drink that number (see above chart). If it is an ace or a 2, finish drinks.</item>
        <item>Shock Aang into the avatar state by making him drink 2. Don\'t laugh though, you drink 2 as well.</item>
        <item>You don\'t like going underground... Haven\'t you heard the song? Drink 2 for courage.</item>
        <item>See generic</item>
        <item>See generic</item>
        <item>See generic</item>
        <item>MANDATORY STOP\nYou are now playing as Toph. Roll the die, roll a 6 and you are playing the rest of the game blind folded. Roll anything else, drink that number of shots of champagne because Aang blasts you off the stage.</item>
        <item>Lose a turn</item>
        <item>I carry my own wieght. Drink: 2 if you weigh between 120 and 200; 4 if under 120 or over 200</item>
        <item>Teach Aang earthbending "The key to earthbending is your stance. You\'ve got to be steady and strong. Rock is a stubborn element. If you\'re going to move it, you\'ve got to be like a rock yourself." Drink 2 shots of cider.</item>
        <item>Roll die, 1-3 hold library and let appa get taken, drink 3. 4-6 let it go, appa still gets taken because you cant see shit, drink 4.</item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
        <item>Toph: "Oh Sokka, you saved me!" Suki: "Actually, it\'s me" Toph: "Oh, well, you can go ahead and let me drown now." 2 shots of Smirnoff.</item>
        <item>Man, it really would have been nice for you to know metalbending at this point... Practice your earthbending and drink 2 shots cider.</item>
        <item>"One doesn\'t just pop in on the Earth King!" One does not simply not get drunk this game, drink 4.</item>
        <item>Bonding time with Katara, you are now mated for the rest of the game for all drinking. (Only on normal drinks, no elemental or finish drinks)</item>
        <item></item>
        <item>Alright, let\'s break some rules! You can now ask questions, and if anyone answers you, they drink.</item>
        <item>Take out a whole earth kingdom army, give out one drink per player in the game.</item>
        <item>"I am the greatest earthbender in the world!" You unlock metalbending, you can now give 1 drink per turn.</item>
        <item>"Just take the bear" See Special Rules (to the right)</item>
        <item>Load the Toph. Drink whatever person to your right gives you to drink.</item>
        <item>Finally, a stylish shoe for the blind earthbender. Take off your shoes and socks. Drink 2 for each item you had to remove.</item>
        <item>Katara and Aang destroy a metal factory and don\'t even tell you about it! Seriously, what the hell? Make them drink 3 a piece.</item>
        <item>"Eh, you\'ve seen nothing once, you\'ve seen it a thousand times." Ok! You are blindfolded until your next turn. (If you are already blind, take if off for the turn)</item>
        <item>Attacked by Sparky Sparky Boom Man! Roll a die, if 1-4, he catches you, drink 3. Otherwise give 1.</item>
        <item>Do you really think friendships can last more than one lifetime? Drink 4 a piece with the person you have been friends with the longest.</item>
        <item>Blindly take one of three shots (Hard Cider, vodka, Water)</item>
        <item>You hear people screaming under the mountain. Drink 3 because I can\'t think of anything for this.</item>
        <item>You da man, Twinkletoes! Give Aang a backhanded compliment and you both drink 2</item>
        <item>You throw up in this episode, lets hope you don\'t do that tonight... Finish your drink.</item>
        <item>MANDATORY STOP\nThree way race between Aang, Toph and Azula, split a hard cider into 3 cups. You must drink, bounce a ball in the cup, and flip it. Losers lose a turn.</item>
        <item>Zuko burns your feet! Take a drink of fireball while Katara rubs them, and make Zuko drink 2 shots of hard cider.</item>
        <item>Learn earthbending from the big bad badgermoles, drink 2 shots of hard cider.</item>
        <item>You didn\'t get any homework</item>
        <item>"Did you at least get some good meat?" You are acting like Sokka, on his next turn you face the same fate as him.</item>
        <item>Help your friends escape, drink half of everyone\'s drink (except finish drinks) until you next turn.</item>
        <item>I release a sonic wave from my mouth... AHHHHHHH... I got a pretty good look at you. Drink 2 shots champagne.</item>
        <item>I am not Toph, I am Melonlord! If you have ever worn a melon on your head, move to the next space, otherwise roll a die, 1-3 move on, 4-6 drink 3.</item>
        <item>"What\'s going on? We\'re surrounded by old people." If you are the youngest playing, move forward. If not, draw a card. If it is a clubs move forward, otherwise stay put and drink half the card\'s value.</item>
        <item>"That\'s a lot of fire... Is\'nt it? Take a shot of fireball and move forward.</item>
        <item>You metalbend the airships to get them to destroy eachother. Bounce a quarter into a shotglass, if you miss, drink the last digit of the year on the quarter and stay put. If you make it, pick someone else to shoot. If they make it, stay put. If they miss, you win the game.</item>
        <item></item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="azulaRules">
        <item>Sorry dude, you aren\'t introduced until episode 3... Drink 2 and GET PUMPED</item>
        <item>Yep, you still haven\'t been introduced... Drink 2, give 1.</item>
        <item>Agni Kai against Zuko, take turns drawing random cards, first to 5 reds wins. Winner drinks 2, loser drinks 1 and loses a turn.</item>
        <item>Still in pain and disgrace from your agni kai against Zuko. Drink 2 and lose a turn</item>
        <item>The fire nation has yet to reach Omashu, drink 1 for each person ahead of you.</item>
        <item>Do a George Takei impression. You drink for each person playing if it sucks or you don\'t know who that is. If it is good, everyone drinks. Props.</item>
        <item>You probably were the one who burned down the forest. You fuckin\' hot head, take 2 shots of smirnoff to cool down.</item>
        <item>If Zuko landed on this square before you, he finishes his drink. You didn\'t fall for his smokescreen for 1 second. Otherwise drink 2 give 2.</item>
        <item>Arrgh! There be Pirates! Talk like a pirate for 3 turns or ye be drinkin!</item>
        <item>Does the Fire Nation let people go? Does the Fire Nation have mercy? Drink 2</item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
        <item>Zhao and Azula are shown on screen at the same time. Until book 2, drink double the drinks you are given.</item>
        <item>Duel both Zuko and Aang. Mini game of flip cup, Zhao has to do 6 cups, Aang and Zuko have to do 3 each.</item>
        <item>That volcano erupted even hotter than your temper. Drink 2 to give props.</item>
        <item>Zhao, you are not in enough episodes. Move forward 1 space.</item>
        <item>Temper is too hot to handle, write the name of something you enjoy on a piece of paper and burn it. Drink 2.</item>
        <item>See generic</item>
        <item>Send pirates after Zuko, drink 3.</item>
        <item>His name\'s Zhao. Middle aged, big sideburns, bigger temper. Draw sideburns on your face and drink 1.</item>
        <item>You get drug under water by a spirit monster, beer bong a shmirnoff ice. You are now playing as Azula.</item>
        <item>Like I\'ve never done that before... Duel Zuko. Split a beer, chugging contest. Loser misses their next turn.</item>
        <item>If the Fire nation catches Zuko, they\'ll hand him over to you... If you land on the same space as Zuko (before Crossroads of Destiny), make him finish his drink.</item>
        <item>See generic</item>
        <item>See generic</item>
        <item>See generic</item>
        <item>Fire Nation Man! "Fire Lord, my flame burns for thee!" Go back to the Fire Nation! Take a shot of hard cider.</item>
        <item>Azula always lies. Tell 2 truths and 1 lie, everyone guesses which is the lie. If wrong, drink 2, if right, give 2.</item>
        <item>You can run, but i will find you. Both you and Aang draw two cards, highest sum wins, if you win, Aang drinks a pull of fireball. If you lose, drink 2 shots of champagne.</item>
        <item>Zuko: " I know what you\'re going to say: she\'s my sister and I should be trying to get along with her." Iroh: "No,She\'s crazy and she needs to go down." Your drink. Finish it.</item>
        <item>Zhao makes a cameo appearance, drink 2 shots of smirnoff for old times sake.</item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
        <item>"Here\'s the deal. I hear the captain\'s eating like a king (the fat, happy kind) while the refugees have to feed off his scraps." Give everyone some food... Or just make them all drink 2.</item>
        <item>Both you and Aang cut the deck of cards, highest card wins (aces high). Loser drinks a mixture of one shot of hard cider and one shot of shmirnoff.</item>
        <item>"And whatever you do, stay away from the Dai Li." The Dai Li are the new villains, drink a shot of cider to prepare yourself.</item>
        <item>Lose a turn</item>
        <item></item>
        <item>Long Feng is bad, but Azula is worse. Until your next turn, whenever anyone drinks, you drink with them.</item>
        <item>"Sleep now, Fire Lord Zuko." Whoever woke up earliest this morning drinks a shot of fireball.</item>
        <item>Looks like everything is going according to plan. Take 1 drink and another turn.</item>
        <item>Challenge with Aang, Katara, and Zuko. See Special Rules (to the right)</item>
        <item>Give Zuko the credit for defeating the avatar, drink 1 from the Avatar State.</item>
        <item>"Mai, Ty Lee needs your help untangling her braid" Sounds serious... Better drink 4.</item>
        <item>The fire nation is polluting the crap out of that river, take a drink of something you don\'t want to take a drink of.</item>
        <item>Some episodes take place in the fire nation but don\'t feature firebenders... Drink 2 I guess.</item>
        <item>MANDATORY STOP\m"We defeated you for all time! You will never rise from the ashes of you shame and humiliation!" Challenge everyone individually to bouncing a ball into a cup. First one to miss loses, loser drinks 3.</item>
        <item>Give Zuko a history lesson. Tell him a cool histoical fact and drink 2 a piece.</item>
        <item>Not in this episode :( drink 2.</item>
        <item>Not in this episode either! Drink 2, or finish your drink if you landed on The Runaway.</item>
        <item>If you\'re here for a royal hair-combing, I\'m afraid you\'ll have to wait. Roll to see who gives you a scalp massage, drink 2 while they do it.</item>
        <item>You\'re so underground, nobody has any idea where you are. Play a song nobody has ever heard. Drink 2 per people who have heard it, if no one has make them drink 1.</item>
        <item>MANDATORY STOP\nThree way race between Aang, Toph and Azula, split a hard cider into 3 cups. You must drink, bounce a ball in the cup, and flip it. Losers lose a turn.</item>
        <item>Zuko should have blamed you for combustion man, next time he has to drink, you drink for him.</item>
        <item>All this firebending and you aren\'t around for it! Finish your drink.</item>
        <item>Mai\'s uncle is the warden, drink 2 because I said so.</item>
        <item>"I\'m a people person" Discover brother and crew, play rock, paper, scissors against Zuko. Loser drinks 2</item>
        <item>"I am about to celebrate becoming an only child" roll a die, 1-5, that person drinks 4; 6, kill everyone, everyone finish their drink.</item>
        <item>Not if my lightning can help it! Whoever "won" thunderstruck drinks.</item>
        <item>Fire Lord Azula? It does seem appropriate. Draw a card. If it is a face card (ace included), move forward. If it isn\'t, copy the last persons drink. If it is a 2, draw again.</item>
        <item>Both Katara and Zuko are coming to stop you. Choose one of them to rock-paper-scissors against. If you win, move forward. If you lose, drink 3.</item>
        <item>Go on a spree of banishing people. You must defeat everyone in the circle. Take turns flipping a cup, if they miss, you defeat them. If you miss twice, you are out. If you fail, drink 3 and stay put. On your next turn you do not need to re-defeat people.</item>
        <item>Katara freezes you, guess what, beer bong another shmirnoff ice. You Win!</item>
        <item></item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="irohRules">
        <item>Firebending gets its power from the breath, not the muscles. Count how many times you breathe until your next turn. Then drink that many.</item>
        <item>Aang almost wakes you up from your nap... (whispers)...Sorry... He can\'t talk until your next turn. You both drink 2.</item>
        <item>So this is how the great commander Zhao acts in defeat... disgraceful! Even in exile my nephew is more honorable then you. Thanks again for the tea. It was delicious. Make Zhao drink 3 and you take a shot of sweat tea vodka</item>
        <item>You decide to hang out on the boat for this episode. Drink 1 and give 2. Make yourself comfortable, you can take anyone\'s seat if you want.</item>
        <item>The fire nation has yet to reach Omashu, drink 1 for each person ahead of you.</item>
        <item>Being sick of tea is like being sick of breathing. take a shot of sweet tea vodka.</item>
        <item>You are clearly outnumbered, you are clearly outmatched. Zuko and Iroh against Aang Katara Sokka and Appa/Momo. 4 cup flip cup, one beer each side. (only do once)</item>
        <item>Being sick of tea is like being sick of breathing. take a shot of sweet tea vodka.</item>
        <item>"Can\'t you see that your own ship has set sail... Maybe it should be a proverb..." Recite your favorite proverb. Drink 2.</item>
        <item>Does the Fire Nation let people go? Does the Fire Nation have mercy? Drink 2</item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
        <item>Redirect lightning! Everyone drink 1.</item>
        <item>Being sick of tea is like being sick of breathing. take a shot of sweet tea vodka.</item>
        <item>I don\'t remember you getting hit... Shhh... Drink 2</item>
        <item>Being sick of tea is like being sick of breathing. take a shot of sweet tea vodka.</item>
        <item>See generic</item>
        <item>Sing 4 seasons... that is all</item>
        <item>This will be nothing like your legendary failure at Ba Sing Se... Take a shot of hard cider.</item>
        <item>"Whatever you do to that spirit, I will unleash upon you tenfold!" Zhao rolls a dice, everyone splits the diceroll X 10 in drinks.</item>
        <item>Redirect Azula\'s lightning. Roll a die, 1-3 she drinks 3, you drink 3. 4-6, she drinks 6.</item>
        <item>Delectable tea... Or deadly poison? Blindly pick between a shot of something tasty, and something not tasty. (Group\'s choice)</item>
        <item>See generic</item>
        <item>See generic</item>
        <item>See generic</item>
        <item>Fire Nation Man! "Fire Lord, my flame burns for thee!" Go back to the Fire Nation! Take a shot of hard cider.</item>
        <item>Being sick of tea is like being sick of breathing. take a shot of sweet tea vodka.</item>
        <item>I poured your tea because i wanted to, and for no other reason. share some wisdom and some of your drink with toph</item>
        <item>Can you feel your own chi flowing in, down, up, and out? ~Come on, you\'ve got to feel the flow~ Drink 2 shots of smirnoff.</item>
        <item>Move forward one space into the desert.</item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
        <item>Who would have thought after all these years, I\'d return to the scene of my greatest military disgrace... As a tourist! Drink 2 and put on a hat.</item>
        <item>"I know you\'re not supposed to cry over spilled tea, but... [Sniffs.] it\'s just so sad!" From this point on, if anyone spills a drink they have to take a shot of fireball.</item>
        <item>"Sick of tea?! That\'s like being sick of breathing!" You know it, you love it. Drink every time you have to breathe until your next turn.</item>
        <item>Listen to Brave Soldier Boy, everyone drink out of respect</item>
        <item></item>
        <item>The Tea Weaville! No... that\'s stupid. take a shot of sweet tea vodka.</item>
        <item>Being sick of tea is like being sick of breathing. take a shot of sweet tea vodka.</item>
        <item>The Jasmine Dragon is open for business, if Zuko has hit this square, you drink 3 together. If not, drink 3 alone.</item>
        <item>Did I ever tell you how I got the nickname "The Dragon of the West?" Roll a die, take half the number of shots of fireball rounding up.</item>
        <item>Being sick of tea is like being sick of breathing. take a shot of sweet tea vodka.</item>
        <item>"You\'re a crazy old man, and if you weren\'t in jail, you\'d be sleeping in a gutter" Lay on the floor until your next turn, and drink 2.</item>
        <item>The fire nation is polluting the crap out of that river, take a drink of something you don\'t want to take a drink of.</item>
        <item>Some episodes take place in the fire nation but don\'t feature firebenders... Drink 2 I guess.</item>
        <item>Being sick of tea is like being sick of breathing. take a shot of sweet tea vodka.</item>
        <item>Being sick of tea is like being sick of breathing. take a shot of sweet tea vodka.</item>
        <item>Not in this episode :( drink 2.</item>
        <item>Not in this episode either! Drink 2, or finish your drink if you landed on The Runaway.</item>
        <item>Being sick of tea is like being sick of breathing. take a shot of sweet tea vodka.</item>
        <item>Getting prepared to bust out of jail. Get your pump on, do 20 pushups, for every 1 you can\'t do drink 1.</item>
        <item>MANDATORY STOP\n"He was like a... One man army." Shotgun a beer.</item>
        <item>"If you keep an open mind, and an open heart, I know you will find your own destiny someday." Find your destiny, roll 2 dice, drink the higher number.</item>
        <item>Conquered the last dragon. Show off your power, drink 3.</item>
        <item>Leaf me alone, I\'m bushed! Tell a joke with a pun and everyone drinks.</item>
        <item>Being sick of tea is like being sick of breathing. take a shot of sweet tea vodka.</item>
        <item>Being sick of tea is like being sick of breathing. take a shot of sweet tea vodka.</item>
        <item>Zuko... It\'s time we had a talk, your hair... It\'s gone too far!!</item>
        <item>Gathering forces to retake Ba Sing Se, take a shot of sweet tea vodka then pour a shot of each element, don\'t drink these yet.</item>
        <item>Still gathering, but almost ready to go. Pull a card, if it is a king, drink what you poured last turn and move forward. If it is not, drink 4 and try again next turn.</item>
        <item>Blow up wall to ba sing se. Mix everyone\'s drinks into a cup and drink it all.</item>
        <item>"My belly isn\'t that big anymore. I\'ve really trimmed down." Go outside and run around the block. I don\'t care what time it is or how big the block is. You cannot win until you do this.</item>
        <item></item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="spaceNames">
        <item>Boy In The Iceberg</item>
        <item>Avatar Returns</item>
        <item>Southern Air Temple</item>
        <item>Warriors of Kyoshi</item>
        <item>The King of Omashu</item>
        <item>Imprisoned</item>
        <item>The Spirit World</item>
        <item>Avatar Roku</item>
        <item>The Waterbending Scroll</item>
        <item>Jet</item>
        <item>The Great Divide</item>
        <item>The Great Divide</item>
        <item>The Great Divide</item>
        <item>The Great Divide</item>
        <item>The Storm</item>
        <item>The Blue Spirit</item>
        <item>The Fortuneteller</item>
        <item>Bato of the Water Tribe</item>
        <item>The Deserter</item>
        <item>The Northern Air Temple</item>
        <item>The Waterbending Master</item>
        <item>Siege of the North 1</item>
        <item>Siege of the North 2*</item>
        <item>The Avatar State</item>
        <item>The Cave of Two Lovers</item>
        <item>Return to Omashu</item>
        <item>The Swamp</item>
        <item>Avatar day</item>
        <item>The Blind Bandit</item>
        <item>Zuko Alone</item>
        <item>The Chase</item>
        <item>Bitter Work</item>
        <item>The Library</item>
        <item>The Desert</item>
        <item>The Desert</item>
        <item>The Desert</item>
        <item>The Serpent’s Pass</item>
        <item>The Drill</item>
        <item>City of Walls and Secrets</item>
        <item>Tales of Ba Sing Se</item>
        <item>Appa’s Lost Days</item>
        <item>Lake Laogai</item>
        <item>The Earth King</item>
        <item>The Guru*</item>
        <item>The Crossroads of Destiny*</item>
        <item>The Awakening</item>
        <item>The Headband</item>
        <item>The Painted Lady</item>
        <item>Sokka’s Master</item>
        <item>The Beach</item>
        <item>The Avatar and the Firelord</item>
        <item>The Runaway</item>
        <item>The Puppet Master</item>
        <item>Nightmares and Daydreams</item>
        <item>The Day of Black Sun part 1-The Invasion</item>
        <item>The Day of Black Sun part 2-The Eclipse*</item>
        <item>The Western Air Temple</item>
        <item>The Firebending Masters</item>
        <item>The Boiling Rock part 1</item>
        <item>The Boiling Rock part 2</item>
        <item>The Southern Raiders</item>
        <item>The Ember Island Players</item>
        <item>Sozin’s Comet part 1-The Phoenix King*</item>
        <item>Sozin’s Comet part 2-Old Masters*</item>
        <item>Sozin’s Comet part 3-Into the Inferno*</item>
        <item>Sozin’s Comet part 4-Avatar Aang*</item>
        <item>End</item>
         </string-array>

    <string name="title_activity_info_screen">Rule</string>

</resources>
